[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. president did Forrest NOT get to meet in person in the movie Forrest Gump?", "correct_answer": "Gerald Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["Lyndon B. Johnson", "John F. Kennedy", "Richard M. Nixon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was not part of Coach Dales practices in the movie Hoosiers?", "correct_answer": "Shooting", "incorrect_answers": ["Defense", "Passing", "Running"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that Yasseir Arafat became chairman of the Palestinian Liberation Organization in 2004?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dolphins are considered some of the most intelligent animals on the planet. How are they classified according to their diet?", "correct_answer": "They are carnivores.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are specialized eaters.", "They are herbivores.", "They are omnivores."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What rapper appeared in the 1997 movie Anaconda as a character named Danny Rich?", "correct_answer": "Ice Cube", "incorrect_answers": ["Coolio", "Tupac Shakur", "Dr. Dre"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animals pilot the airplane to Africa in the 2008 animated comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "Penguins", "incorrect_answers": ["A lemur and an Aye-aye", "A hippopotamus and a giraffe", "A zebra and a lion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film St. Elmos Fire, what is the major colour of Jules apartment?", "correct_answer": "Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Orange", "Yellow", "Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Johnny Dangerously, what did Johnny give his mother for her 29th birthday?", "correct_answer": "an ashtray", "incorrect_answers": ["a cartoon of cigarettes", "an iron", "a sweater"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Once the dingo was introduced to Australia, the Thylacine population decreased steadily until the only viable populations were on the Island of Tasmania.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Goldfish are good parents. They nurse and protect their young until they grow up enough to defend themselves.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are wild turkeys very good fliers?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one is not a name of a Galilean moon revolving around Jupiter?", "correct_answer": "Athena", "incorrect_answers": ["Io", "Europa", "Callisto"]}]